Excuse me. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me. Coming through.
Tonight, so-called
magician Lionel shrike
is making another sad
attempt for attention
by performing what he calls
an impossible feat.
The safe is made of
the strongest iron.
It can't be sawed
through or pried.
Yet, Lionel shrike thinks
he's able to escape.
Dad! Dad!
Hey, buddy.
You made it, huh?
Now, see that seat there?
Is Lionel shrike
the kind of magician
who can pull this off?
Or is he actually
in over his head?
We'll see about that.
What's the matter?
I don't want you to go.
Dylan, come on.
We talked about this.
Remember?
This is what I do.
I got to prove all
those naysayers wrong.
Okay? Besides...
I always keep
something up my sleeve.
Now, got your watch
like your dad's?
Okay. How many seconds?
300.
300. Maybe a few less.
Mmm.
I love you so much.
Okay.
See you later, big man.
- Ladies and gentlemen,
- Lionel shrike!
Will he be able
to hold his breath?
Will he be able to
somehow escape the safe?
Three, two, one...
Two, three,
four, five, six,
seven, eight...
296...
297, 298, 299, 300.
303, 304...
It's five minutes now,
and we have not
seen or heard anything
from Lionel shrike yet.
Move!
Dad!
Dad! Dad!
Let go of me!
Dad!
No! Dad!
Dad! Let go!