1
00:00:05,856 --> 00:00:06,823
(GROANING)

2
00:00:06,924 --> 00:00:07,924
(MEN SHOUTING)

3
00:00:11,395 --> 00:00:12,395
Robb!

4
00:00:13,263 --> 00:00:14,263
Ahh !

5
00:00:19,837 --> 00:00:20,803
(ROARING)

6
00:00:20,904 --> 00:00:21,904
-(SCREAMING)
-(MEN CHEERING)

7
00:00:26,343 --> 00:00:27,343
(SCREECHING)

8
00:00:40,724 --> 00:00:41,824
(SCREECHING)

9
00:00:41,925 --> 00:00:43,125
Season Three begins with

10
00:00:43,227 --> 00:00:46,863
us very much heading in the right direction.

11
00:00:46,964 --> 00:00:48,097
(SCREECHING)

12
00:00:48,198 --> 00:00:50,032
The dragons have got a bit bigger.

13
00:00:50,467 --> 00:00:54,003
And you're starting to see
what they'II end up becoming.

14
00:00:54,104 --> 00:00:55,371
We're headed to Astapor because

15
00:00:55,472 --> 00:00:57,139
we've got our ships
and now we need an army.

16
00:00:57,241 --> 00:01:00,076
Some say the UnsuIIied
are the greatest soIdiers in the worId.

17
00:01:00,177 --> 00:01:02,044
The greatest sIave-soIdiers in the worId.

18
00:01:02,145 --> 00:01:05,314
She debates whether
the UnsuIIied wouId truIy be behind her

19
00:01:05,415 --> 00:01:07,383
because she's paid them to.

20
00:01:07,584 --> 00:01:10,620
DAENERYS:
Once I own an army of sIaves, what wiII I be?

21
00:01:10,754 --> 00:01:13,456
Pyat Pree has sent a warIock
to try and kiII me,

22
00:01:13,557 --> 00:01:16,125
and I'm saved by Ser Barristan SeImy.

23
00:01:16,393 --> 00:01:18,528
The honour is mine, my queen.

24
00:01:18,729 --> 00:01:20,463
CLARKE: He pIedges aIIegiance to me

25
00:01:20,564 --> 00:01:23,966
because he was head of the Kingsguard
for my father.

26
00:01:24,067 --> 00:01:27,670
I have been searching for you,
Daenerys Stormborn, to ask your forgiveness.

27
00:01:27,771 --> 00:01:29,739
I wiII not faiI you again.

28
00:01:31,575 --> 00:01:34,176
Ygritte's taking him to meet Mance Rayder.

29
00:01:34,278 --> 00:01:37,313
And this is going
straight into enemy territory.

30
00:01:37,414 --> 00:01:40,883
He doesn't rate his chances of survivaI
particuIarIy high.

31
00:01:40,984 --> 00:01:43,152
Don't Iook so grim, Jon Snow.

32
00:01:43,253 --> 00:01:45,922
If Mance Rayder Iikes you,
you'II Iive another day.

33
00:01:46,056 --> 00:01:47,089
And if he don't. . .

34
00:01:47,190 --> 00:01:50,760
When Jon first waIks into Mance's camp,
he meets Tormund.

35
00:01:50,861 --> 00:01:52,695
What do we want with a baby crow?

36
00:01:52,796 --> 00:01:55,431
This baby kiIIed Qhorin HaIfhand.

37
00:01:55,532 --> 00:01:57,233
HARINGTON: Mance is a Iegendary figure.

38
00:01:57,334 --> 00:01:58,935
He used to be part of the Night's Watch.

39
00:01:59,036 --> 00:02:01,037
MANCE:
Why do you want to join us?

40
00:02:01,138 --> 00:02:04,507
I saw Craster take his own baby boy
and Ieave it in the woods.

41
00:02:04,608 --> 00:02:05,641
I saw what took it.

42
00:02:05,742 --> 00:02:07,944
And why wouId that make you
desert your brothers?

43
00:02:08,245 --> 00:02:11,781
I want to fight for the side
that fights for the Iiving.

44
00:02:12,015 --> 00:02:14,584
Do you know how Iong it'II take
to get to King's Landing

45
00:02:14,685 --> 00:02:16,285
waIking through fieIds and forests?

46
00:02:16,386 --> 00:02:17,553
BRIENNE:
Yes.

47
00:02:17,654 --> 00:02:19,021
One thing Jaime is very good at,

48
00:02:19,122 --> 00:02:22,058
he's very good at sniffing
out peopIe's weaknesses.

49
00:02:22,125 --> 00:02:23,159
Move.

50
00:02:23,260 --> 00:02:25,127
COSTER-WALDAU:
He wants her to Iose it with him

51
00:02:25,228 --> 00:02:29,365
so that he wiII get the opportunity
to get out of his chains and get rid of her.

52
00:02:29,466 --> 00:02:33,703
And then they reach this bridge
and finaIIy he gets the opportunity.

53
00:02:33,870 --> 00:02:35,471
(JAIME GRUNTS)

54
00:02:38,508 --> 00:02:39,642
(BRIENNE GRUNTS)

55
00:02:40,077 --> 00:02:41,110
COSTER-WALDAU: It is unbeIievabIe.

56
00:02:41,211 --> 00:02:44,714
He goes from one bad situation
to a horribIe situation,

57
00:02:44,815 --> 00:02:47,683
so we have the wonderfuI Locke appear.

58
00:02:47,784 --> 00:02:50,286
Let us go
and my father wiII pay you whatever you want.

59
00:02:50,887 --> 00:02:52,521
Enough to buy me a new head?

60
00:02:55,125 --> 00:02:56,492
Season Three starts with

61
00:02:56,593 --> 00:02:58,828
Robb reaIIy just wanting to fight someone.

62
00:02:59,229 --> 00:03:02,431
And they get to HarrenhaI and, again,
he can't fight anyone.

63
00:03:02,532 --> 00:03:04,000
And worse than that,

64
00:03:04,334 --> 00:03:08,738
the peopIe IoyaI to him have been sIaughtered
in a most horrific way.

65
00:03:09,506 --> 00:03:11,907
Find her a chamber that wiII serve as a ceII.

66
00:03:12,009 --> 00:03:13,442
TALISA: She's your mother.

67
00:03:13,543 --> 00:03:14,944
ROBB: She freed Jaime Lannister.

68
00:03:15,078 --> 00:03:18,814
The Lannisters robbed them of their sons
and she robbed them of their justice.

69
00:03:18,915 --> 00:03:21,517
When we arrive, I get the message

70
00:03:21,618 --> 00:03:26,188
that WinterfeII, after being taken by Theon,
has now been burned to the ground,

71
00:03:26,289 --> 00:03:29,158
and it Iooks Iike Bran
and Rickon may be dead.

72
00:03:29,259 --> 00:03:32,428
By the time BoIton's bastard got to WinterfeII,
the ironborn were gone.

73
00:03:32,529 --> 00:03:34,930
They massacred everyone
and put the castIe to the torch.

74
00:03:35,032 --> 00:03:36,699
And Bran and Rickon have not been found.

75
00:03:36,800 --> 00:03:38,501
MICHELLE FAIRLEY:
Bran and Rickon have fIed WinterfeII

76
00:03:38,602 --> 00:03:40,770
and no one has heard from them.

77
00:03:40,871 --> 00:03:43,039
But, there's a brother and a sister that come.

78
00:03:43,140 --> 00:03:46,475
I'm Jojen Reed. This is my sister, Meera.

79
00:03:46,576 --> 00:03:48,210
We've come a Iong way to find you, Brandon.

80
00:03:48,445 --> 00:03:52,281
They reaIise he has this power,
but he doesn't know anything about it.

81
00:03:52,382 --> 00:03:53,983
JOJEN:
And we have much farther to go.

82
00:03:54,084 --> 00:03:55,484
So it's about educating him

83
00:03:55,585 --> 00:03:58,421
so that he can actuaIIy become
what he becomes.

84
00:03:58,522 --> 00:04:01,057
Theon may have taken them
back to the Iron IsIands as hostages.

85
00:04:01,158 --> 00:04:03,693
Have you heard anything from Theon at aII?

86
00:04:05,762 --> 00:04:06,762
What's your name?

87
00:04:06,863 --> 00:04:08,097
Theon Greyjoy.

88
00:04:08,565 --> 00:04:09,565
(GROANS)

89
00:04:11,168 --> 00:04:14,770
What is your name?

90
00:04:15,272 --> 00:04:16,338
Reek.

91
00:04:16,573 --> 00:04:17,773
My name is. . .

92
00:04:18,475 --> 00:04:19,575
Reek.

93
00:04:20,043 --> 00:04:23,579
MAISIE WILLIAMS: First of aII,
they're in the woods trying to find her famiIy.

94
00:04:23,680 --> 00:04:25,314
Not necessariIy home,

95
00:04:25,415 --> 00:04:28,751
just somewhere
where she thinks her famiIy may be.

96
00:04:28,852 --> 00:04:31,220
And they come across the Brotherhood.

97
00:04:33,190 --> 00:04:34,190
They don't know who she is.

98
00:04:34,291 --> 00:04:36,292
They don't reaIIy want anything
to do with her.

99
00:04:36,460 --> 00:04:37,893
You can finish your meaIs before you go.

100
00:04:37,994 --> 00:04:39,929
-You'II free us?
-I gave you my word.

101
00:04:40,030 --> 00:04:41,630
RORY McCANN:
The Hound had been drinking too much.

102
00:04:41,732 --> 00:04:44,166
We know he's an angry man and a bit Iost.

103
00:04:44,267 --> 00:04:45,301
I mean, where's the Hound gonna go?

104
00:04:45,469 --> 00:04:49,238
So I think he was found drunk under a tree
with not aII his wits about him.

105
00:04:49,339 --> 00:04:53,609
Just as she's this cIose from the door,
the Hound recognises who she is.

106
00:04:53,677 --> 00:04:54,710
GirI.

107
00:04:54,811 --> 00:04:56,946
Then teIIs the rest of the Brotherhood
who she is.

108
00:04:57,047 --> 00:05:00,716
What in seven heIIs
are you doing with the Stark bitch?

109
00:05:03,653 --> 00:05:06,222
Sansa finds a new friend in Season Three.

110
00:05:06,289 --> 00:05:07,289
Margaery.

111
00:05:07,390 --> 00:05:10,192
MARGAERY:
It is my honour to present my grandmother.

112
00:05:11,428 --> 00:05:13,629
The Lady OIenna of House TyreII.

113
00:05:13,730 --> 00:05:15,631
Pretty much
as soon as she's introduced to them,

114
00:05:15,732 --> 00:05:17,066
they taIk about Joffrey.

115
00:05:17,167 --> 00:05:22,404
I want you to teII me the truth
about this royaI boy, this Joffrey.

116
00:05:23,140 --> 00:05:25,641
Sansa teIIs them what he's reaIIy Iike.

117
00:05:25,709 --> 00:05:26,742
He's a monster.

118
00:05:27,344 --> 00:05:28,344
Ah.

119
00:05:28,745 --> 00:05:30,246
That's a pity.

120
00:05:30,413 --> 00:05:31,447
TeII me what you think of her.

121
00:05:31,515 --> 00:05:32,548
Who?

122
00:05:32,616 --> 00:05:33,616
Margaery.

123
00:05:33,717 --> 00:05:34,750
She's an ideaI match.

124
00:05:34,851 --> 00:05:38,254
With the TyreIIs beside us,
we'II crush the Northerners.

125
00:05:38,355 --> 00:05:40,723
The new reIationship
between Margaery and Joffrey,

126
00:05:40,824 --> 00:05:42,358
I think, scares Cersei a Iot.

127
00:05:42,459 --> 00:05:44,226
Cersei's reaIIy threatened by Margaery

128
00:05:44,327 --> 00:05:47,396
'cause she's younger and she's more
beautifuI. She's very smart.

129
00:05:47,531 --> 00:05:50,499
But Cersei sees aII that.
She knows she's a game pIayer.

130
00:05:50,600 --> 00:05:54,170
She married a traitor and known degenerate
Iike RenIy Baratheon for a reason.

131
00:05:54,271 --> 00:05:57,573
She married RenIy Baratheon
because she was toId to.

132
00:05:58,241 --> 00:06:01,143
That's what inteIIigent women do.
What they're toId.

133
00:06:01,244 --> 00:06:03,279
This is what
these seasons are becoming about,

134
00:06:03,380 --> 00:06:06,215
is her Ioss of that one thing
that kept her sane,

135
00:06:06,316 --> 00:06:07,316
because she beIieves him.

136
00:06:07,417 --> 00:06:10,386
He's gonna be the next king
and she wouId reign through him.

137
00:06:10,687 --> 00:06:13,856
The Lord of HarrenhaI wiII make
a worthy suitor for the widow Arryn.

138
00:06:13,957 --> 00:06:16,025
For which I am extremeIy gratefuI to you.

139
00:06:16,126 --> 00:06:20,162
You'II Ieave for the Eyrie as soon as possibIe
and bring Lysa Arryn into the foId.

140
00:06:20,263 --> 00:06:22,264
PETER DINKLAGE:
Tywin wants to secure everything.

141
00:06:22,365 --> 00:06:24,767
And he figured
LittIefinger wouId be a great person

142
00:06:24,868 --> 00:06:26,769
to go up there and take charge.

143
00:06:26,870 --> 00:06:29,471
LITTLEFINGER: Lady Arryn and I have
known each other since we were chiIdren.

144
00:06:29,573 --> 00:06:34,276
She has aIways been
positiveIy predisposed toward me.

145
00:06:34,878 --> 00:06:38,647
TYRION: But Lord BaeIish's absence
wouId present certain probIems.

146
00:06:38,949 --> 00:06:43,552
The royaI wedding may end up being
the most expensive event in Iiving memory.

147
00:06:43,653 --> 00:06:46,856
Not a good time
to Ieave the crown's finances unattended.

148
00:06:47,357 --> 00:06:50,392
Which is why I'm naming you
new Master of Coin.

149
00:06:50,760 --> 00:06:53,696
DINKLAGE:
They sort of don't reaIIy recognise Tyrion

150
00:06:54,164 --> 00:06:57,499
as being so instrumentaI
in saving King's Landing.

151
00:06:57,934 --> 00:07:01,036
The rebeIs came for Joffrey's head,
they Iost their own.

152
00:07:01,137 --> 00:07:02,171
Thanks to Father.

153
00:07:02,439 --> 00:07:04,073
Thanks to Father.

154
00:07:04,774 --> 00:07:08,544
The UnsuIIied,
who are fundamentaIIy a sIave army,

155
00:07:08,645 --> 00:07:10,746
do exactIy as they're toId.

156
00:07:11,548 --> 00:07:12,548
When she meets the UnsuIIied,

157
00:07:12,649 --> 00:07:15,684
she reaIises that she wiII take the UnsuIIied

158
00:07:16,653 --> 00:07:18,454
if onIy to save them.

159
00:07:18,588 --> 00:07:20,723
There's a smaII amount of bartering
that goes on

160
00:07:20,824 --> 00:07:22,858
untiI she kind of puIIs out the ace of spades.

161
00:07:23,360 --> 00:07:25,794
I have dragons. I'II give you one.

162
00:07:25,996 --> 00:07:29,932
When she hands over the dragon,
she swaps the dragon for the whip,

163
00:07:30,033 --> 00:07:31,767
which means that she's the master.

164
00:07:31,868 --> 00:07:35,404
So she teIIs them
they need to kiII aII of the sIavers.

165
00:07:43,647 --> 00:07:44,680
Dracarys.

166
00:07:45,382 --> 00:07:46,682
(SCREAMING)

167
00:07:48,318 --> 00:07:49,351
(SCREECHING)

168
00:07:51,721 --> 00:07:52,888
-MANCE: OreII.
-(GASPING)

169
00:07:52,989 --> 00:07:54,156
HARINGTON: OreII, he's a warg,

170
00:07:54,257 --> 00:07:56,258
and he can Iook through the eyes of

171
00:07:56,359 --> 00:07:57,927
his animaI, which is an eagIe.

172
00:07:58,028 --> 00:08:02,131
He reports back that he's seen dead crows
at the Fist of the First Men.

173
00:08:02,632 --> 00:08:06,268
When we reach the Fist of the First Men,
we discover that

174
00:08:06,369 --> 00:08:07,670
there's a kind of horrific pattern

175
00:08:07,771 --> 00:08:09,605
of dead horses that's been made.

176
00:08:09,706 --> 00:08:14,009
And Mance is quick to point out
that this is the work of the White WaIkers.

177
00:08:14,110 --> 00:08:15,911
AIways the artists.

178
00:08:16,146 --> 00:08:19,782
Mance decides
that Jon shouId go with the cIimbing party

179
00:08:19,849 --> 00:08:20,883
over the WaII

180
00:08:20,984 --> 00:08:22,117
for the basic reason that

181
00:08:22,218 --> 00:08:25,020
Jon knows more about the WaII
than anybody eIse.

182
00:08:25,121 --> 00:08:28,857
If he's usefuI, good.
If not, throw him off the WaII.

183
00:08:29,059 --> 00:08:30,726
See if crows can fIy.

184
00:08:31,561 --> 00:08:33,162
These men, aII these soIdiers,

185
00:08:33,263 --> 00:08:35,864
they've been on the road
for God knows how Iong.

186
00:08:35,966 --> 00:08:37,833
And now, suddenIy they have this woman.

187
00:08:37,934 --> 00:08:40,302
Jaime knows what's going to happen.
He knows before it happens.

188
00:08:40,403 --> 00:08:43,472
But then when it does happen, he. . .

189
00:08:43,573 --> 00:08:46,041
For some reason, I think it surprises himseIf,

190
00:08:46,142 --> 00:08:49,478
he can't just stand by,
so he makes up this story.

191
00:08:49,579 --> 00:08:51,547
Her father is Lord SeIwyn Tarth.

192
00:08:51,982 --> 00:08:56,719
Lord SeIwyn wouId pay his daughter's weight
in sapphires if she's returned to him.

193
00:08:56,820 --> 00:08:58,821
COSTER-WALDAU:
So, Locke thinks about that

194
00:08:58,922 --> 00:09:02,424
and his greed is stronger than his Iust,
I guess.

195
00:09:02,525 --> 00:09:04,693
So he takes it out on Jaime instead.

196
00:09:06,730 --> 00:09:08,797
(SCREAMING)

197
00:09:09,599 --> 00:09:13,736
MADDEN: We get the news
that Robb's grandfather is dead at Riverrun.

198
00:09:13,837 --> 00:09:16,538
Robb's very much aware
that he needs the army

199
00:09:16,639 --> 00:09:19,308
that his mother's famiIy command, as weII.

200
00:09:19,409 --> 00:09:23,145
So they set off to go to Riverrun
for the funeraI of his grandfather

201
00:09:23,246 --> 00:09:24,780
and to discuss what happens next.

202
00:09:24,881 --> 00:09:26,248
And when we get there,

203
00:09:26,349 --> 00:09:31,020
Robb meets again the BIackfish
and Edmure, CateIyn's brother.

204
00:09:31,121 --> 00:09:34,023
Edmure has come up with
two Lannister prisoners.

205
00:09:34,124 --> 00:09:36,025
EDMURE: WiIIem Lannister. Martyn Lannister.

206
00:09:36,126 --> 00:09:38,494
WiIIem and Martyn Lannister are 1 4 years oId.

207
00:09:38,595 --> 00:09:41,096
Lord Karstark takes it upon himseIf,
during the night,

208
00:09:41,197 --> 00:09:45,300
to sIaughter these two young boys
chained up in a prison ceII.

209
00:09:45,402 --> 00:09:47,269
Robb understands why he's done it.

210
00:09:47,370 --> 00:09:51,640
But as a king and as a just Ieader,
he can't aIIow that to go unpunished.

211
00:09:52,042 --> 00:09:54,510
Rickard Karstark, I sentence you to die.

212
00:09:54,778 --> 00:09:55,778
(GRUNTS)

213
00:09:56,212 --> 00:09:58,580
When Robb carries out the sentence
on Lord Karstark,

214
00:09:58,681 --> 00:10:00,049
Robb Ioses haIf his army.

215
00:10:00,450 --> 00:10:01,950
-The Karstarks are gone.
-(CLATTERING)

216
00:10:02,952 --> 00:10:05,287
They need more men. They need heIp.

217
00:10:05,388 --> 00:10:07,689
He needs to make amends
with peopIe he's betrayed,

218
00:10:07,791 --> 00:10:08,857
which is the Freys.

219
00:10:08,958 --> 00:10:11,527
But because of
Robb's breaking of his promise

220
00:10:11,628 --> 00:10:12,795
by marrying TaIisa

221
00:10:12,896 --> 00:10:16,832
when he had been promised to
one of WaIder Frey's daughters,

222
00:10:17,033 --> 00:10:21,303
they are very scepticaI
about approaching WaIder Frey.

223
00:10:21,404 --> 00:10:22,871
And rightIy so.

224
00:10:23,073 --> 00:10:25,574
He sends two sons as an envoy.

225
00:10:25,675 --> 00:10:29,111
And WaIder Frey has said,
"Yes, we wiII heIp you."

226
00:10:29,546 --> 00:10:31,880
But the sting in the taiI is that

227
00:10:31,981 --> 00:10:35,384
Edmure must marry
one of WaIder Frey's daughters.

228
00:10:35,618 --> 00:10:38,087
-CouId I see her first?
-You want to count her teeth?

229
00:10:38,188 --> 00:10:39,388
FAIRLEY: He's disgusted because

230
00:10:39,489 --> 00:10:41,590
everybody in the Iand knows that

231
00:10:41,691 --> 00:10:44,827
nobody in any right mind
wouId want to marry a Frey.

232
00:10:46,896 --> 00:10:49,965
The Brotherhood take her to see their Ieader.

233
00:10:50,066 --> 00:10:52,801
His name is Beric Dondarrion.

234
00:10:53,069 --> 00:10:54,570
WILLIAMS:
She's not particuIarIy happy about it,

235
00:10:54,671 --> 00:10:57,706
but they're not hurting her,
so it couId be worse.

236
00:10:57,807 --> 00:11:01,477
He's a knight,
but he's with aII these guys in rags

237
00:11:01,578 --> 00:11:03,846
and they Iook Iike a bunch of swineherds.

238
00:11:03,980 --> 00:11:06,648
If you mean to murder me,
then bIoody weII get on with it.

239
00:11:06,749 --> 00:11:09,151
You'II die soon enough,
but it won't be murder.

240
00:11:09,352 --> 00:11:13,589
For some bizarre reason,
they choose a triaI by combat.

241
00:11:15,458 --> 00:11:16,625
(BOTH GRUNTING)

242
00:11:18,428 --> 00:11:21,930
WILLIAMS:
Beric gets a sword down his shouIder

243
00:11:22,031 --> 00:11:25,334
and toppIes over and "dies."

244
00:11:25,969 --> 00:11:29,938
But somehow, Beric Dondarrion is born again

245
00:11:30,039 --> 00:11:32,007
with the heIp of Thoros.

246
00:11:32,108 --> 00:11:34,476
It was reaIIy pretty spooky stuff.

247
00:11:34,777 --> 00:11:36,345
How many times have you brought me back?

248
00:11:36,446 --> 00:11:38,080
It's the Lord of Light who brings you back.

249
00:11:38,181 --> 00:11:40,048
-How many times?
-This makes six.

250
00:11:40,150 --> 00:11:41,183
What are you going to do with me?

251
00:11:41,284 --> 00:11:44,520
At first Iight we'II ride for Riverrun.
Your brother's there now.

252
00:11:44,621 --> 00:11:47,356
What have we here? Frozen crows?

253
00:11:47,557 --> 00:11:48,790
We can taIk inside.

254
00:11:48,958 --> 00:11:50,225
Can we?

255
00:11:50,326 --> 00:11:52,561
HARINGTON: Mormont and
a depIeted group of other rangers

256
00:11:52,662 --> 00:11:54,930
make it back to Craster's Keep aIive.

257
00:11:55,031 --> 00:11:57,833
BLACK BROTHER:
Bet you feed that pig better than you feed us.

258
00:11:57,934 --> 00:11:59,501
Pig's got vaIue to me.

259
00:11:59,602 --> 00:12:00,569
(WOMAN SCREAMING)

260
00:12:00,670 --> 00:12:02,404
(BABY CRYING)

261
00:12:04,607 --> 00:12:07,409
It's at this point the rebeIIion starts.

262
00:12:07,510 --> 00:12:08,510
(SHOUTING)

263
00:12:09,179 --> 00:12:11,146
-MORMONT: I shaII have your head.
-(GRUNTS)

264
00:12:13,116 --> 00:12:14,883
SAMWELL:
We have to go. Now!

265
00:12:16,519 --> 00:12:18,253
I now am a woman on a mission.

266
00:12:18,354 --> 00:12:20,689
I've saved 8,000 sIaves

267
00:12:20,790 --> 00:12:24,760
and I've got a thirst
for wanting to save more peopIe.

268
00:12:24,861 --> 00:12:26,261
So we move on to Yunkai.

269
00:12:26,362 --> 00:12:29,665
BARRISTAN: The Yunkish train bed sIaves,
not soIdiers. We can defeat them.

270
00:12:29,766 --> 00:12:31,366
But they won't meet us on the fieId.

271
00:12:31,634 --> 00:12:33,101
They have strong waIIs.

272
00:12:38,408 --> 00:12:40,876
So I then set up camp

273
00:12:40,977 --> 00:12:43,912
and hear the sIavers of Yunkai,

274
00:12:44,013 --> 00:12:46,148
and I kind of Iay down the Iaw for them.

275
00:12:46,249 --> 00:12:48,951
You wiII reIease every sIave in Yunkai.

276
00:12:49,352 --> 00:12:53,055
Reject this gift,
and I shaII show you no mercy.

277
00:12:53,189 --> 00:12:54,523
You are mad.

278
00:12:54,691 --> 00:12:57,726
We are not Astapor or Qarth. We are Yunkai.

279
00:12:57,927 --> 00:13:00,729
Those who survive,
we shaII ensIave once more.

280
00:13:00,930 --> 00:13:03,098
Perhaps we'II make a sIave of you as weII.

281
00:13:03,266 --> 00:13:04,666
(SCREECHING)

282
00:13:06,202 --> 00:13:07,469
Now get out.

283
00:13:07,670 --> 00:13:09,638
CLARKE: I give them a IittIe bit of a fright
with the dragons,

284
00:13:09,739 --> 00:13:14,209
and then I decide that I'm going to kiII them.

285
00:13:15,745 --> 00:13:19,014
HARINGTON: Before Jon, Ygritte,
Tormund and OreII cIimb the WaII,

286
00:13:19,115 --> 00:13:24,086
Ygritte sort of coerces Jon
into a secret pIace she knows. . .

287
00:13:24,153 --> 00:13:25,220
Ygritte!

288
00:13:25,321 --> 00:13:27,155
And decides to reaIIy test,

289
00:13:27,257 --> 00:13:30,092
A, whether he's a crow,
and B, whether he Ioves her.

290
00:13:30,193 --> 00:13:32,427
I don't ever want to Ieave this cave, Jon Snow.

291
00:13:32,528 --> 00:13:35,364
HARINGTON: And Jon does betray his vows.

292
00:13:35,765 --> 00:13:38,834
I think it's at that point
that he faIIs in Iove with Ygritte.

293
00:13:38,935 --> 00:13:40,702
It's a rare moment in the story

294
00:13:40,803 --> 00:13:44,239
where we have a pureIy happy moment
between two characters.

295
00:13:45,008 --> 00:13:47,876
When Jon and the others
are cIimbing the WaII,

296
00:13:47,977 --> 00:13:49,945
which is 800 feet of ice,

297
00:13:50,046 --> 00:13:52,147
a part of the WaII breaks off,

298
00:13:52,248 --> 00:13:55,150
Ieaving Jon dangIing on the end of a rope,

299
00:13:55,251 --> 00:13:56,318
as weII as Ygritte.

300
00:13:57,353 --> 00:14:01,056
And it's onIy right at the Iast minute
that Jon manages to save them both.

301
00:14:01,257 --> 00:14:02,491
(HORSE WHINNYING)

302
00:14:04,027 --> 00:14:06,528
FinaIIy, they get to HarrenhaI, to the castIe.

303
00:14:06,629 --> 00:14:09,398
Lord BoIton, I give you the KingsIayer.

304
00:14:09,899 --> 00:14:12,367
We have a dinner with Roose BoIton.

305
00:14:12,468 --> 00:14:14,770
BOLTON:
I wiII aIIow you to go to King's Landing

306
00:14:14,937 --> 00:14:17,839
as restitution
for the mistakes my soIdiers made.

307
00:14:17,940 --> 00:14:19,541
And you wiII swear to teII your father

308
00:14:19,642 --> 00:14:21,710
that I had nothing to do with your maiming.

309
00:14:21,778 --> 00:14:22,744
My Iady.

310
00:14:22,845 --> 00:14:24,546
She won't be going with you.

311
00:14:24,647 --> 00:14:28,016
When Jaime Ieaves HarrenhaI,
he Ieaves with a bad taste in his mouth.

312
00:14:28,117 --> 00:14:29,851
I'm Ieaving her with Locke.

313
00:14:29,952 --> 00:14:34,389
Don't you worry about your friend.
We'II take good care of her.

314
00:14:34,490 --> 00:14:36,325
But then on the road, he finds out

315
00:14:36,426 --> 00:14:38,427
that it's onIy a matter of time
and they're gonna kiII her.

316
00:14:38,528 --> 00:14:40,929
And he again surprises himseIf,

317
00:14:41,030 --> 00:14:43,065
the way he so wants to just not care.

318
00:14:44,233 --> 00:14:45,233
(ROARING)

319
00:14:45,335 --> 00:14:47,402
But he does and he goes back.

320
00:14:47,537 --> 00:14:50,539
We're taking her to King's Landing.
UnIess you kiII me.

321
00:14:51,974 --> 00:14:54,109
WeII, we must be on our way.

322
00:14:54,744 --> 00:14:57,012
Spotted a Lannister raiding party.

323
00:14:57,113 --> 00:14:59,014
-How far?
-Less than a day's ride south.

324
00:14:59,115 --> 00:15:00,716
Time for a Iion hunt?

325
00:15:00,883 --> 00:15:03,318
They say,
"Oh, we're gonna go and kiII some Lannisters

326
00:15:03,419 --> 00:15:04,920
"and then we'II take you home."

327
00:15:05,021 --> 00:15:07,456
-I swear to you, this isn't. . .
-You're a Iiar.

328
00:15:07,557 --> 00:15:10,058
They're aII distracted
getting on their armour and things Iike that,

329
00:15:10,159 --> 00:15:12,627
so she sees her opportunity
and she goes for it.

330
00:15:13,496 --> 00:15:16,264
MAN 1 : Anguy, bring her back.
MAN 2: Come back, girI !

331
00:15:16,699 --> 00:15:19,034
WILLIAMS: Then gets stopped by the Hound.

332
00:15:21,170 --> 00:15:22,671
Kick aII you Iike, woIf girI.

333
00:15:23,172 --> 00:15:24,873
Won't do you no good.

334
00:15:24,974 --> 00:15:29,544
He sees a chance of
using Arya as a bargaining chip.

335
00:15:29,645 --> 00:15:30,912
Is that the BIackwater?

336
00:15:31,047 --> 00:15:34,015
That's the Red Fork.
I'm taking you to the Twins.

337
00:15:34,250 --> 00:15:36,518
Your uncIe is marrying one of the Frey girIs.

338
00:15:36,619 --> 00:15:40,422
Your mother and brother wiII be there,
and they'II pay me for you.

339
00:15:40,823 --> 00:15:43,158
So a great road trip begins.

340
00:15:43,993 --> 00:15:47,496
LittIefinger comes aIong and he says to Sansa

341
00:15:47,597 --> 00:15:50,465
he's got a ship
and he couId take her with him.

342
00:15:50,633 --> 00:15:53,135
PIease, Lord BaeIish. TeII me what to do.
TeII me when.

343
00:15:53,236 --> 00:15:56,304
She yet again thinks
she's gonna get out of here.

344
00:15:56,406 --> 00:15:57,739
You must see Highgarden.

345
00:15:57,840 --> 00:16:00,142
I don't think the Queen
wouId Iet me Ieave King's Landing.

346
00:16:00,243 --> 00:16:04,780
Margaery wants to marry Sansa off
to her brother Loras TyreII.

347
00:16:04,881 --> 00:16:06,748
Once I marry Joffrey, I'II be queen.

348
00:16:06,849 --> 00:16:10,285
And if you were to marry Loras. . .

349
00:16:10,386 --> 00:16:12,888
Which Sansa is over the moon about.

350
00:16:12,989 --> 00:16:15,957
She's getting married to a guy
that's actuaIIy nice.

351
00:16:16,058 --> 00:16:19,995
The TyreIIs are pIotting
to marry Sansa Stark to Ser Loras.

352
00:16:20,263 --> 00:16:22,898
We need to find Sansa Stark
a different husband.

353
00:16:22,999 --> 00:16:26,067
He teIIs Tyrion he's gonna marry Sansa,
which I find hiIarious.

354
00:16:26,169 --> 00:16:27,903
Then, kind of within the same breath,

355
00:16:28,004 --> 00:16:31,106
Iets me know that
I'II be marrying Margaery's brother.

356
00:16:31,207 --> 00:16:33,375
Tyrion wiII do as he's bid. As wiII you.

357
00:16:33,476 --> 00:16:34,443
What do you mean?

358
00:16:34,544 --> 00:16:35,544
You'II marry Ser Loras.

359
00:16:35,912 --> 00:16:37,512
-I wiII not.
-Yes, you wiII.

360
00:16:37,613 --> 00:16:40,949
This arranged marriage to Sansa
doesn't go over very weII.

361
00:16:41,050 --> 00:16:42,984
She doesn't Iike that news at aII.

362
00:16:43,085 --> 00:16:47,088
She wasn't gonna go on LittIefinger's ship
because she was being married to Loras.

363
00:16:47,190 --> 00:16:49,057
Now LittIefinger has saiIed away,

364
00:16:49,158 --> 00:16:52,828
she's getting married to Tyrion,
who she didn't want to get married to.

365
00:16:52,929 --> 00:16:55,597
So, am I invited to your wedding?

366
00:16:55,698 --> 00:16:59,100
Shae is pretty gutted
about this marriage to Tyrion.

367
00:16:59,202 --> 00:17:01,837
EspeciaIIy now that
she's Sansa's handmaiden.

368
00:17:01,938 --> 00:17:03,839
Listen to me, my Iady.

369
00:17:03,940 --> 00:17:04,940
I'm not your Iady.

370
00:17:05,041 --> 00:17:06,441
I'm your whore.

371
00:17:06,542 --> 00:17:08,143
DINKLAGE: He's vuInerabIe, Tyrion,

372
00:17:08,344 --> 00:17:10,879
and that's very frightening to him.

373
00:17:11,481 --> 00:17:14,950
The wedding to Tyrion, in Sansa's eyes,

374
00:17:15,117 --> 00:17:16,685
it was the worst day of her Iife.

375
00:17:16,786 --> 00:17:19,387
He's a Lannister. She's not gonna trust him.

376
00:17:19,489 --> 00:17:22,691
Joffrey, of course,
takes great gIee in this new reIationship

377
00:17:22,792 --> 00:17:25,660
and torments both of them,
as he usuaIIy does.

378
00:17:26,162 --> 00:17:27,863
JOFFREY: Time for the bedding ceremony.

379
00:17:27,930 --> 00:17:28,930
ALL: Ah !

380
00:17:29,031 --> 00:17:30,765
TYRION:
There wiII be no bedding ceremony.

381
00:17:30,867 --> 00:17:33,168
There wiII be if I command it.

382
00:17:35,538 --> 00:17:38,740
TYWIN: I'm sure Tyrion did not mean
to threaten the King.

383
00:17:38,975 --> 00:17:41,843
Your uncIe is cIearIy quite drunk, Your Grace.

384
00:17:42,278 --> 00:17:43,411
Stop.

385
00:17:43,513 --> 00:17:44,613
But your father. . .

386
00:17:44,714 --> 00:17:46,047
I won't share your bed.

387
00:17:46,148 --> 00:17:47,749
Not untiI you want me to.

388
00:17:47,850 --> 00:17:49,684
What if I never want you to?

389
00:17:49,785 --> 00:17:51,786
And so my watch begins.

390
00:17:56,325 --> 00:17:58,627
OnIy one oId man and eight good horses.

391
00:17:58,728 --> 00:17:59,761
Let's carve him up.

392
00:17:59,862 --> 00:18:01,162
We just take the horses and go.

393
00:18:02,031 --> 00:18:03,632
The oId man's no threat.

394
00:18:03,900 --> 00:18:05,100
There's a storm coming.

395
00:18:05,201 --> 00:18:06,334
(THUNDER RUMBLING)

396
00:18:07,036 --> 00:18:09,538
It's as good a pIace to sheIter as any.

397
00:18:12,842 --> 00:18:14,109
WiIdIings.

398
00:18:14,911 --> 00:18:20,415
Bran and Rickon and Osha and Hodor are
in the windmiII that is just by where Jon is.

399
00:18:20,516 --> 00:18:23,985
Their paths just miss each other.
Neither of them know that they're there.

400
00:18:24,086 --> 00:18:26,788
ORELL: Cut his throat,
or he'II teII the crows we're here.

401
00:18:26,889 --> 00:18:28,523
HARINGTON: The man has to be kiIIed

402
00:18:28,624 --> 00:18:32,060
and it's OreII who suggests
that it shouId be Jon who does it

403
00:18:32,161 --> 00:18:34,162
to prove that he's a wiIdIing.

404
00:18:38,134 --> 00:18:39,167
KiII him.

405
00:18:39,235 --> 00:18:40,235
(GRUNTS)

406
00:18:40,870 --> 00:18:45,173
OreII and Tormund are about to kiII Jon
when two direwoIves attack.

407
00:18:45,341 --> 00:18:49,411
It's Bran who goes into his warg mode
and into Summer

408
00:18:49,512 --> 00:18:52,080
to attack the wiIdIings and save Jon.

409
00:18:53,549 --> 00:18:54,616
-(DIREWOLF GROWLS)
-(SCREAMS)

410
00:18:56,285 --> 00:18:57,852
-(GRUNTS)
-(GROANS)

411
00:18:57,954 --> 00:18:58,954
(SCREECHING)

412
00:19:05,394 --> 00:19:07,562
MADDEN: When we arrive at the Freys',

413
00:19:07,663 --> 00:19:11,066
Lord Frey wants to make sure
that this wedding happens here and now

414
00:19:11,167 --> 00:19:12,834
before we go back to war.

415
00:19:12,935 --> 00:19:14,836
Or so that's what we're Ied to beIieve.

416
00:19:14,937 --> 00:19:18,239
If you think the time is right, Lord WaIder,
by aII means,

417
00:19:18,307 --> 00:19:19,274
Iet us bed them.

418
00:19:19,375 --> 00:19:23,411
As the bedding party exits, the Iights dim.

419
00:19:23,779 --> 00:19:27,983
Then, IiteraIIy, as the door cIoses,
the band strike up.

420
00:19:28,084 --> 00:19:31,353
And that is what makes CateIyn turn around
and think, "What is going on here?

421
00:19:31,454 --> 00:19:33,254
"Something is about to happen."

422
00:19:33,356 --> 00:19:36,958
(PLAYING THE RAINS OF CASTAMERE)

423
00:19:37,059 --> 00:19:40,395
Arya compIeteIy beIieves
that she's going home.

424
00:19:40,730 --> 00:19:43,231
She's with one of the most
powerfuI guys she's ever met

425
00:19:43,332 --> 00:19:45,233
and he actuaIIy is trying to heIp her.

426
00:19:45,334 --> 00:19:47,369
This is our chance
of getting into the wedding

427
00:19:47,470 --> 00:19:49,604
by using the saIt pork wagon.

428
00:19:49,705 --> 00:19:51,973
Turn this cart around
and get the heII out of here.

429
00:19:52,842 --> 00:19:55,176
Lord WaIder then stops the proceedings.

430
00:19:55,277 --> 00:19:58,747
FAIRLEY: Roose BoIton comes over
to the tabIe and sits beside CateIyn,

431
00:19:58,848 --> 00:20:02,550
and that's when
the enormity of the situation strikes her.

432
00:20:03,619 --> 00:20:04,653
Robb!

433
00:20:06,222 --> 00:20:07,222
(GROANS)

434
00:20:08,424 --> 00:20:09,424
(GROANS)

435
00:20:11,527 --> 00:20:13,495
This sea of arrows come at them.

436
00:20:14,030 --> 00:20:17,565
And WaIder Frey is basicaIIy enjoying
every moment of this.

437
00:20:17,700 --> 00:20:20,101
Just as we're coming in,
everyone was kiIIing each other.

438
00:20:20,202 --> 00:20:23,471
WILLIAMS: She reaIises everything is
going wrong and she doesn't even know why.

439
00:20:23,572 --> 00:20:24,839
So it was time, change of pIan.

440
00:20:24,940 --> 00:20:26,975
PIan B. Get the heII out of there.

441
00:20:27,076 --> 00:20:28,143
HOUND:
It's too Iate.

442
00:20:28,244 --> 00:20:29,210
McCANN: The Hound, at the Iast minute,

443
00:20:29,311 --> 00:20:31,946
manages to just grab her from behind
and knock her out.

444
00:20:33,849 --> 00:20:37,085
At the same time,
CateIyn is trying to say to her son, "Get out,"

445
00:20:37,186 --> 00:20:39,587
but he won't Ieave his dying wife.

446
00:20:39,689 --> 00:20:40,722
Mother.

447
00:20:41,857 --> 00:20:43,591
FAIRLEY: Roose BoIton waIks up to Robb

448
00:20:43,693 --> 00:20:46,227
and whispers something in his ear
and then stabs him.

449
00:20:46,328 --> 00:20:48,763
The Lannisters send their regards.

450
00:20:49,098 --> 00:20:50,432
And she just Ioses it.

451
00:20:50,599 --> 00:20:51,900
(WAILING)

452
00:20:59,709 --> 00:21:02,043
GLEESON: When Joffrey gets the news
of the Red Wedding,

453
00:21:02,144 --> 00:21:03,812
this is the best day of his Iife.

454
00:21:03,913 --> 00:21:06,214
I waIk into the SmaII CounciI chamber

455
00:21:06,315 --> 00:21:08,683
and everyone eIse sort of knows
what has happened.

456
00:21:08,751 --> 00:21:09,984
I don't.

457
00:21:10,219 --> 00:21:11,753
KiIIed a few puppies today?

458
00:21:11,854 --> 00:21:13,788
Robb Stark is dead.

459
00:21:14,090 --> 00:21:15,623
Joffrey Ioves every second of it.

460
00:21:15,725 --> 00:21:18,793
Command Lord Frey
to send Robb Stark's head.

461
00:21:18,894 --> 00:21:21,529
I'm going to serve it to Sansa
at my wedding feast.

462
00:21:21,630 --> 00:21:23,631
She is no Ionger yours to torment.

463
00:21:23,733 --> 00:21:27,235
Everyone is mine to torment,
you IittIe monster.

464
00:21:27,403 --> 00:21:33,241
Monsters are dangerous,
and just now kings are dying Iike fIies.

465
00:21:33,542 --> 00:21:35,777
She finds out that her

466
00:21:35,878 --> 00:21:38,680
brother and her mother have been kiIIed.

467
00:21:38,748 --> 00:21:39,748
Sansa.

468
00:21:39,849 --> 00:21:41,349
TURNER: It is very unexpected.

469
00:21:41,450 --> 00:21:43,485
AII her hopes are dashed,
Iike, every singIe time.

470
00:21:43,586 --> 00:21:45,386
She is pretty bitter.

471
00:21:45,855 --> 00:21:49,758
The usurper Robb Stark is dead.
Betrayed by his bannerman.

472
00:21:49,859 --> 00:21:54,496
Despite his Ioss at BIackwater,
the threat of Stannis is stiII present.

473
00:21:54,630 --> 00:21:56,531
DAVOS: It's from Maester Aemon
of the Night's Watch.

474
00:21:56,632 --> 00:21:58,366
Their Lord Commander is dead.

475
00:21:58,467 --> 00:22:03,171
What he saw beyond the WaII,
it's coming for aII of us.

476
00:22:03,272 --> 00:22:07,175
Stannis appears to be more determined
in his desire for the throne.

477
00:22:07,276 --> 00:22:10,078
MELISANDRE:
This War of Five Kings means nothing.

478
00:22:10,346 --> 00:22:12,747
The true war Iies to the north, my King.

479
00:22:12,915 --> 00:22:14,449
Death marches on the WaII.

480
00:22:14,550 --> 00:22:16,284
OnIy you can stop him.

481
00:22:16,852 --> 00:22:18,920
So, Sam and GiIIy
head towards the WaII together

482
00:22:19,021 --> 00:22:20,555
to go back to the Night's Watch.

483
00:22:20,723 --> 00:22:22,690
SAMWELL:
The Nightfort's cIosest to CastIe BIack.

484
00:22:22,792 --> 00:22:24,893
It's got a secret saIIy port.

485
00:22:24,994 --> 00:22:28,229
It Ieads through the WaII
right down into the Nightfort.

486
00:22:28,330 --> 00:22:30,832
-MEERA: It's empty.
-Let's find a pIace to sIeep.

487
00:22:32,067 --> 00:22:34,502
So they come across Bran and Hodor.

488
00:22:34,603 --> 00:22:37,272
Come with us.
We'II waIk straight to CastIe BIack.

489
00:22:37,406 --> 00:22:38,640
Take us north of the WaII.

490
00:22:38,741 --> 00:22:40,208
Why in the worId wouId you want to go. . .

491
00:22:40,309 --> 00:22:42,410
I don't want to. I have to.

492
00:22:45,381 --> 00:22:49,117
Now he comes back to King's Landing
and, of course, no one recognises him.

493
00:22:49,552 --> 00:22:51,085
Step aside, country boy.

494
00:22:51,187 --> 00:22:53,288
He makes it up to Cersei.

495
00:22:53,389 --> 00:22:55,490
And then he sees her.
They just Iook at each other.

496
00:22:55,658 --> 00:22:58,927
This is reaIIy the moment
where he reaIIy reaIises that

497
00:22:59,028 --> 00:23:00,795
"I'm no Ionger the same man."

498
00:23:00,896 --> 00:23:05,200
She's ecstatic because she's got
the one person she trusts back.

499
00:23:05,367 --> 00:23:09,370
But he comes in missing
the thing that makes him who he is as a man.

500
00:23:09,538 --> 00:23:11,039
They're both a bit Iike, "Who are you?"

501
00:23:11,140 --> 00:23:13,441
There's a Iot happened
since they haven't seen each other.

502
00:23:13,542 --> 00:23:16,411
After Jon escapes, Ygritte catches up to him.

503
00:23:16,512 --> 00:23:17,979
JON:
I have to go home now.

504
00:23:18,080 --> 00:23:19,480
I know you won't hurt me.

505
00:23:19,849 --> 00:23:21,583
You know nothing, Jon Snow.

506
00:23:23,419 --> 00:23:24,452
(GRUNTS)

507
00:23:26,288 --> 00:23:27,288
(GRUNTS)

508
00:23:27,790 --> 00:23:30,358
Jon survives and we find him
right at the end of Season Three,

509
00:23:30,459 --> 00:23:33,228
coIIapsing off his horse
and being dragged into CastIe BIack.

510
00:23:33,329 --> 00:23:34,495
Carry him inside.

511
00:23:34,730 --> 00:23:37,799
And we Ieave him,
not knowing whether he'II be safe or not.

512
00:23:38,934 --> 00:23:40,268
CLARKE: Under the cover of nightfaII,

513
00:23:40,369 --> 00:23:43,571
I send my best men in
through a side entrance

514
00:23:43,672 --> 00:23:45,106
to the city of Yunkai

515
00:23:45,207 --> 00:23:47,942
and have them murder aII of the sIavers.

516
00:23:48,210 --> 00:23:50,645
And so that
they can then reIease aII the sIaves.

517
00:23:50,746 --> 00:23:52,580
When she finds that they've been successfuI,

518
00:23:52,681 --> 00:23:55,450
they come back
to wait outside the gates of Yunkai

519
00:23:55,551 --> 00:23:57,318
to see what the faIIout wiII be.

520
00:23:57,419 --> 00:24:01,356
And then the sIaves come out
and the person they see is Dany,

521
00:24:01,457 --> 00:24:03,291
the woman who's saved them.

522
00:24:03,492 --> 00:24:05,360
-Mhysa!
-ALL: Mhysa!

523
00:24:05,461 --> 00:24:07,929
CLARKE: The word that comes out
of their mouth is "mhysa,"

524
00:24:08,030 --> 00:24:09,097
which means "mother."

525
00:24:09,198 --> 00:24:12,667
And it's this moment that Dany,
for the first time,

526
00:24:12,835 --> 00:24:15,670
sees what her new dream is going to be

527
00:24:15,771 --> 00:24:19,440
and she reaIises the possibiIity of
how many more there are to save.

528
00:24:19,608 --> 00:24:22,977
And it's this wonderfuI moment
of them Iooking to her as a mother

529
00:24:23,078 --> 00:24:25,413
and her kind of accepting their Iove

530
00:24:25,514 --> 00:24:26,848
and becoming a Ieader.

